大家好 我是Sheldon Cooper博士
Hello. I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
欢迎收看Sheldon Cooper主持的旗乐无穷
And welcome to Sheldon Cooper Presents: Fun with Flags,
今天给您带来的是最后一集 旗观
the Final Episode Flagtacular.
我知道有这个特效 不过还是有点怕呢
I knew it was coming. Still scary.
我知道你们现在一定在想 "最后一期?
Now, I'm sure you're thinking, "The final episode?
那以后谁来带领我们走出对国旗的无知呢“
Who will stand between us and flag ignorance"
对啊 我就是这么想的
I know I was thinking that.
这个节目是讲国旗的还是读心的?
Is this a show on flags or mind reading?
我做出这个决定是因为 我无法同时做一份全职工作
But the truth is I can no longer balance a full-time career,
主持一档广受欢迎的网络节目 并对付一个女朋友
a popular Internet show, and a girlfriend.
告诉你们这些喷子 他真的有女朋友
And he really does have one, you jerks on the comment board.
正如人们所说的那样 再美好的事情也有结束的一天
So as they say, all good things must come to an end.
我们在短短232期节目之后就要说再见了
After only 232 episodes.
其实算上某人忘记按下录像键的那次
233 if we include the one
应该一共有233期的
somebody forgot to press record on.
你说你不会再提了
You said you weren't gonna bring that up.
你还说你按录像键了呢
And you said you pressed record.
这些都不重要 请大家放松心情
Anyway, please sit back, relax,
和我们共同享受这个节目的最后一段旅程...
and join us as we take our final lap...
挥动的竞赛用旗也是在告诉大家这是最后一次了
as indicated by the waving of this racing flag.
当然 白色的旗子也可以用来代表投降
And, of course, white flags can also represent surrender,
刚铎的首相 还有日本源氏部落
the Stewards of Gondor, and the Japanese Minamoto clan,
不过第六十二期节目里面也讲过了
but I'm sure you remember that from episode 62,
“白色旗帜: 谁的白旗在挥及为什么在挥”
"White Flags: Who's Waving Them and Why"
那期特别好
That was a good one.
简直太棒了
It was so good.
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第八季第10集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 影子   时间轴: 。沫
校对: UU2222222了
翻译：酥酥爱土豆 喵嗷呗 Astral Navy Seal 柱君
我还以为收拾一个去世的教授的办公室
You know, I thought cleaning out a dead professor's office
仅仅是会比较无聊
was gonna just be boring,
可是我看到了他的假牙
but then I found his dentures
就发现这件事还有点恶心
and realized it's also gross.
Abbott教授的家人不想留着这些吗?
Doesn't Professor Abbott's family want any of this stuff?
他好像没有家人
I don't think he had a family.
- 好惨啊  - 我知道
- That's rough.  - I know.
你可以工作一辈子
You can spend your whole life working,
到最后剩下的不过是这个箱子里的一堆纸
and at the end all that's left are some papers in a box.
这种事真的会让人想很多
Makes you think.
管他呢
Oh, well.
嘿 嘿 我们应该先检查一下这些东西
Hey. Hey, we're supposed to look through all this stuff
然后再扔的 万一有重要的资料呢
before we throw it away in case it's important.
我... 我检查过了 都是过时的或者被证伪的理论
I... I did. It's all outdated or disproved.
可能吧 不过这支钢笔证明了重力
I don't know. This old pen kind of proves gravity.
倒过来的时候 这个女人身上的泳衣就会脱下来
When I tilt it, her bathing suit falls right off.
哇哦
Oh,
我老爸也有一根这样的钢笔
my dad used to have a pen like that.
是我小学前六年的约会对象呢
I dated it all through sixth grade.
就这样扔掉他的东西
It still feels weird
感觉还是怪怪的
just throwing away his work like this.
别这样 总有一天
Don't feel bad. Someday,
也会有人把你的心血扔掉的
someone will be throwing out your work, too.
那个人就是Sheldon 那一天就是昨天
That someone was Sheldon, and the day was yesterday.
嘿 看这个啊
Hey, look at this.
"亲爱的Roger 在你有重大发现的时候打开这瓶酒吧
"Dear Roger, to be opened upon your first great discovery.
爱你的 妈妈"
Love, Mom."
哇 你看这个日期
Wow, look at the date.
他存了五十年却从来没能打开这瓶酒
He saved this 50 years and never got to open it.
好悲伤
That's intense.
可怜的Roger Abbott
Poor Roger Abbott.
Roger Abbott念起来有点像兔子罗杰(卡通人物)
Roger Abbott sounds just like Roger Rabbit.
Roger Abbott Roger Abbott 好像真有点像
Roger Abbott, Roger Abbott, Roger Abbott.
天啊 Leonard 我知道他去世了 但是你试试 真的好好玩!
Oh, my God, Leonard, I know he's dead, but try it. It's fun!
Roger Abbott 兔子罗杰 真的啊...
Roger Abbott, Roger Abbott...
嘿 Penny!
Penny!
年度销售之星啊
Oh, my rookie of the year.
哦 Dan 你当初还不想雇我来着
Oh, Dan. My boss who didn't want to hire me
现在抱我都抱不够
and now's a little hug machine.
哦 看看你 一个新来的
Oh, look at you. Brand-new
就已经是业绩第三的销售了
and already the third best sales rep.
- 你来坐在我这边吧  - 好啊
- Why don't you come over to my table.  - Yes.
我一会就过去 Bernadette正在停车呢
I'll be right there. Bernadette's just parking the car.
哦 这样啊
Oh, good.
Bernadette 可爱的 讨人喜欢的...
Bernadette. Cute, sweet...
邪恶的小Bernadette
vicious little Bernadette.
别这样 她没那么可怕
Come on. She's not that bad.
哦 是吗?
Oh, yeah?
公司野餐的时候 她朝我和我孙子开启了咆哮模式
At the company picnic she yelled at me and my grandson
就因为我们输了两人三足跑比赛
for losing the three-legged race.
我孙子现在还是叫她 "童颜巨乳刻薄妹"
I mean, he still calls her "that mean kid with the big boobies."
我知道她比较强势 但是 我发誓
I know she can be a little intense, but, I swear,
- 她人很好的 只要你无视那些...  - 嘿
- she is so sweet once you get past all the...  - Hey,
你们在说啥呢?
what are you talking about?
噢 我们在说
Oh. We were just talking
我们多爱和你一起工作 是不是啊?
about how much we love working with you. Isn't that right?
Dan呢?
Dan?
录制了这么多年的"旗乐无穷"
Over the years here at Fun With Flags,
我们学过 笑过 好奇过...
we've had an opportunity to learn, laugh, wonder...
是的 还掉过眼泪
And, yes, even shed a tear or two.
比如说你做了个两小时的国庆豪华版特别节目
Like when you do a two-hour Fourth of July spectacular
还没被录下来的时候
and it doesn't get recorded.
我要说多少次对不起才行?
How many times do I have to say I'm sorry?
4000次咋样?
How about 4,000?
对我用来搭美国国旗的每块多米诺骨牌 道歉
One for every domino I set up to make that American flag.
请欣赏以下集锦
Please enjoy these highlights.
矮油! 今天我们有啥旗帜?
Crikey! What flag do we have today?
澳大利亚国旗 伙计!
Australia, mate!
接下来是竞速猜环节 "是不是旗帜"
And now it's time for the speed round of Flag or Not a Flag.
斯 斯
Flag. Flag.
不斯 斯
Not a flag. Flag.
哥玩这个真是超神了
I am crushing this.
贝琪・罗斯女士 你在忙什么呢?
Say, Betsy Ross, what you working on?
伦家也不知道
I have no idea.
因为伦家缝制第一个美国国旗的故事
Because the story of me sewing the first American flag
完全就是无凭无据的瞎扯淡呢
is unsupported poppycock.
那是谁缝制的呢 嗯?
Then who did sew it, hmm?
不要问我
Don't ask me.
我只是个出来赚外快的...
I'm just a simple seamstress whose descendants are...
裁缝后代!
out to make a quick buck!
想游泳吗 亲爱的?
Fancy a dip, my dear?
想啊
I do.
等等 那个紫色旗帜代表
Wait, that purple flag indicates
有海洋有害生物出没 比如水母
that marine pests, such as jellyfish, are present.
哇 那个旗帜真是能救命
Wow, that flag is a lifesaver.
不
No.
这才是
This is.
别盯着我腿看了
Stop looking at my legs.
不斯 斯的
Not a flag. Flag.
斯的 不斯
Flag. Not a flag.
斯的
Flag.
该死
Crap.
当一些东西让我消沉的时候
When stuff like this gets me down,
你知道我都怎么做吗?
you know what I like to do?
和一个八岁萝莉一样 唱"哈库那玛塔塔"?
Sing "Hakuna Matata" like an eight-year-old girl?
"狮子王"插曲 动画片"丁满和彭彭"的主题曲
不对 机灵鬼
Wrong, smarty-pants.
是"乐高大电影"里的"一切都超赞"
It's "Everything Is Awesome" from The Lego Movie.
看看这些笔记本
Look at these notebooks.
满页都是数据
They're full of pages and pages of data.
肯定是他好多年心血
He clearly spent years on this.
嗯 这只是一列列随机数 扔吧
Mmm. Oh, it's just columns of random numbers. Toss it.
但是 万一这里面就藏着他潜在的成就呢?
Well, but what if this was a potential breakthrough for him?
假如... 假如这就是
What if... what if this is the thing
让他打开那瓶香槟的契机呢?
that would've finally let him open that bottle of champagne?
也许他找不到可以配那瓶香槟的东西
Maybe he didn't know what to pair champagne with.
草莓 鱼子酱 牡蛎 都是不错的选择
Strawberries, caviar, oysters. All good choices.
是的 就你那表情
Yeah, that look right there
怪不得大家去你家聚会前都得自己填饱肚子
is why people eat before they come to your parties.
这一定意味着什么
This has to mean something.
看不到可辨别的模型
Well, there's no discernible pattern that I can see,
但是把数字输进去检查应该不难
but it shouldn't be too hard to run the numbers and check.
也许下次可以放到超级计算机上试试
Well, maybe we can get some time on the supercomputer.
是啊 可以试试多元回归分析
Sure. We could try multiple regressions
用不同的物理和试验常数试试
with varying physical and experimental constants.
哦 我们可以对知名的待解决物理难题
Oh, we could run a pattern-matching algorithm
跑一遍模式匹配算法
against well-known unsolved physics problems.
哦 这可能是个替换式密码
Ooh, it might be a substitution cipher.
我们可以先用基本的"密分"
We could start with basic cryptanalysis.
或者问问这个和他一个办公室的人
Or we could talk to this guy he used to share an office with.
好吧 去问问
Oh, let's do that.
因为你不知道怎么"密码分析" 是不是?
Because you don't know how to do cryptanalysis, do you?
我都不知道是不是叫密分
I'm not even sure if it's the right word.
那么
So,
Dan 你有个孙子啊 他多大了?
Dan, you have a grandson. How old is he?
- 七岁  - 哦 是的
- Seven.  - Oh, yeah.
我记得他 一起野餐过
I remember him from the picnic.
他是那个一直哭的孬种
He was the one crying like a wuss the whole time.
我听说他被一个贱小孩给骂了
I heard he was being picked on by a mean kid.
越挫越勇
Just builds character.
就像我爸说的那样 "没人喜欢爱哭鬼
Like my dad said, "Nobody likes a crybaby
除了亲娘和民主党们"
except their mommies and Democrats."
我得再续一杯
I need another drink.
- 他怎么了?  - 哦
- What's his problem?  - Oh.
不知道 也许他不喜欢
I don't know. Maybe he didn't like the fact
你把他的孙子叫成孬种
that you called his grandson a wuss.
好吧 不是不能说"娘娘腔"这个词了吗
Well, I didn't think you were supposed to say "sissy" anymore.
听着 我知道你是个好人
Okay, look, I know what a good person you are,
但是有些人觉得你有点太冲了
but sometimes people think you might come off a little harsh.
什么?
What?
我是我所知道的最可爱的人
I'm, like, the sweetest person I know.
看着我 我该坐在树洞里烤饼干
Look at me. I should be in a tree baking cookies.
是的 但是偶尔
Yes, but once in a while,
有些人觉得你有点刻薄
people think you're a little mean.
是吗?
Oh, yeah?
你也这么觉得?
You one of those people?
不 不 不 不
No. No, no, no.
我...我觉得你该烤饼干
I...I think the cookie thing.
开拍
Action.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
我们今天的客人是个回归的人气王
Our guest today is a returning fan favorite.
是他成就了Reading Rainbow
He puts the reading in your rainbow,
星际迷航里的Geordi La Forge
the Geordi in your La Forge,
还有Roots里的Kunta Kinte
and the Kunta in your Kinte,
他就是LeVar Burton先生
Mr. LeVar Burton.
谢谢 Sheldon 不要忘了我们的约定...
Thank you, Sheldon. Now, remember our deal...
等这个拍完了 我就把你的联系方式删掉
You do this, I delete your contact information.
而且...
While...
而且当场删给你看
While you watch me do it.
太棒了 能回来我很高兴
Great. Happy to be back.
既然你在这里
Well, since you're here,
我想请教一下你对一件事的看法
I'd like to get your opinion on something.
为了庆祝黑人历史月
In honor of Black History Month,
我在一段致敬视频里饰演了卡弗
I portrayed George Washington Carver
但被我的室友说成"极端的种族歧视"
in a loving tribute that my roommate called "wildly racist"
你觉得怎么样?
What do you think?
你好 我叫George
Hi. My name is George.
哦 天哪不是吧!
Oh, hell, no!
你听到他说的了 Leonard
You heard him, Leonard.
不是 这不是种族歧视
No, it's not racist.
真的是在这里吗?
Are we sure this is the place?
看门的人说就是这幢楼
The doorman said this is the right building.
我觉得在吊裤子的人
I think if you're pulling up your pants,
不太像是看门人吧
you're not a doorman.
谁啊?
Who is it?
Sharpe教授在吗?
Uh, I'm looking for a Professor Sharpe?
等等
Hold on.
- 怎么了?  - 嗨
- Can I help you?  - Hi.
我们是大学里来的 我们想了解一下
We're from the university. We're trying to get some information
Abbott教授
about Professor Abbott.
我们在打扫他的办公室的时候
We were cleaning out his office
找到了这些写满了数字的本子
and found these books full of numbers.
你知道那是什么吗?
Any chance you know what it is?
知道 他总是在研究这个 哦
Yes, he was always working on this. Oh.
我想这个可能是
I was thinking it might be
某种星际坐标系统
some sort of interstellar coordinate system,
也有可能是一个升级版的哈勃定律
maybe an updated version of Hubble's law.
我看到90这个数字一直在重复
I keep seeing the number 90 repeating.
这可能是一个遥远星系的
That could be the angle of perturbation
摄动角度
of a distant galaxy.
这是一杯酸奶的卡路里值
It's the number of calories in a yogurt.
这是他的进食日记
That's his food diary.
真的?
Really?
是的 他不管吃了什么都写下来
Yeah, he wrote down everything he ever ate.
他相信控制卡路里摄入量
He was convinced that calorie restriction was the key
是永生的关键
to living forever.
有用吗?
Does it work?
你逗我呢?
Seriously?
他可能是被公交车撞死的 你怎么知道
Well, he could have been hit by a bus. You don't know.
真是对不起 这东西那么无趣
Sorry it's not more interesting.
看开点 你不需要
On the bright side, you didn't have to listen
听他肚子咕咕叫35年
to his stomach growl for 35 years.
Abbott教授有没有研究过什么
So, was there anything that Professor Abbott worked on
真的能有点成果的东西?
during his life that came close to an accomplishment?
老实说 他的研究从来没成什么大气
To be honest, his research never amounted to anything.
哦 你曾经是他的同事
Oh. You were his colleague.
你的研究怎么样?
How did your research turn out?
很棒 嘿 得了诺贝尔奖
Great. Hey, this is the apartment you get
才能买得起这种公寓
when you win a Nobel.
你可以再节省一点的
Well, you could be very frugal.
我已经有点受够了大家的反话了
I'm getting a little tired of everybody's sarcasm.
我不欺负人的
I'm not a bully.
我是说 也许我看上去很强势
I mean, maybe I come off a little strong,
那只是因为我爸爸从小就让我坚强
but that's only because my dad raised me to be tough
不受任何人的侮辱
and not to take crap from anybody.
那也没关系 但是坚强不等于告诉你的朋友
No. That's fine, but there's a difference between being tough
她的新裤子看起来就像松垮的尿不湿
and telling your friend her new pants look like a saggy diaper.
我真那么说了 好像?
I did say that, didn't I?
是的 你说了
Yeah, you did.
我感到很没面子 不得不把裤子退了
I felt so self-conscious, I had to return them.
退哪儿去了? 孕婴店吗?
Where? To Babies R Us?
你又来了!
You're doing it again!
真对不起 我们走行吗?
Okay, sorry. Can we just go?
我感觉每个人都讨厌我
I feel like everybody hates me.
别瞎想 他们不讨厌你 知道吗?
Oh, come on, they don't hate you, all right?
他们就是有点儿怕你
They're just a little intimidated.
你只要让他们看到真实的你
All you need to do is show everyone
有多善良就行了
how sweet you really are.
- 我还是想走  - 不 别走
- I think I'd rather go.  - No, come on.
你哪儿也不能去 知道吗?
You are not going anywhere, all right?
我在这陪着你 咱们一起解决这个问题
I am here for you, and we are gonna fix this together.
谢谢你
Thank you.
尽管你穿的裙子很丑
Even though your dress is ugly.
好啦 我可爱的旗友们
Well, my little Flag-keteers,
看来我们最后一期"旗乐无穷"要接近尾声了
it looks like the last episode of Fun with Flags is at an end.
我真的很希望
If I could,
我能把每一个观众都升到旗杆子上
I would run each and every one of you viewers up a flagpole
然后向你们敬礼
and salute you.
如果你们落在了地上 就烧了你们
And if you touched the ground, burn you.
据传言说美国国旗如果碰到地面就要被烧毁
我还要以我个人的名义
I'd like to take a moment
感谢Amy Farrah Fowler博士
to personally thank Dr.Amy Farrah Fowler,
你们可能不知道
who you may or may not know
她是第一个协助主持了国旗或旗帜类
is the first woman to co-host a flag or banner-related
网络娱乐资讯节目的女人
Internet info-tainment show.
男权 统统滚一边
Take that, glass ceiling.
接下来说点儿正经的
And if I may get serious for a moment,
主持这个节目就像是一次...
hosting this show has been...
不平凡的旅程
one crazy ride.
尽管经历了很多挫折
With all its ups and downs,
可我无论如何都不会放弃
I wouldn't give it up for the world.
除了现在 我正要放弃
Except for now, when I'm giving it up.
在节目结束之前 我想...
Before I sign off, I'd, uh...
我想跟你们所有人分享白旗的最后一个用法
I'd like to share with you all one last use for a white flag.
这种时刻用起来刚好
It's good for times like this.
晚安
Good night.
切
Cut.
噢Sheldon...
Sheldon...
太感人了
that was beautiful.
如果你没按录像键...
If you didn't press record...
老娘按了!
I pressed it!
结束了
Well, that's it.
Roger Abbott就这样收场了
That's the end of Roger Abbott.
而我们还不知道他有什么成就
And we still don't know who framed him.
我还是在想
I still keep thinking
人这一辈子看起来怎么那么一事无成
about how an entire life can seemingly amount to nothing.
我觉得令人悲伤的现实是
I guess the sad truth is,
不是所有的人都会有所成就
not everyone will accomplish something great.
我们中的一些人
Some of us
也许只能从生命中的平凡时刻
may just have to find meaning
去寻找生命的意义了
in the little moments that make up life.
这种想法也不错
That's a nice way of looking at it.
对你是不错 不适用于我
Yeah for you, not for me.
哥儿已经上过太空了 跟你不一样
I went to space. I'm covered.
猜我想到了什么?
You know what?
这瓶香槟是用来庆祝成就的
This bottle was meant to celebrate an achievement.
咱们来做个约定
Let's make a pact.
我们当中有人实现了第一个重大成就的时候
When one of us gets their first big breakthrough,
我们就打开这瓶香槟来庆祝
we'll celebrate by opening this bottle of champagne
并向Abbott祝酒
and toasting Professor Abbott.
好主意
I love that.
Yeah, me, too.
当然还要
Then, of course,
拿我们的成就 喷Sheldon一脸
rubbing our success in Sheldon's face.
- 噢 那才是最棒的  - 对
- Oh, well, that's the best part.  - Oh, yeah.
Dan 我能跟你聊几句吗?
Dan, could I talk to you for a minute?
可以 说吧
Sure, go ahead.
我想让你知道我并不是有意
Just want you to know I didn't mean
对你的外孙那么没礼貌的
to be rude about your grandson.
没关系
No, it's okay.
不 有关系
No, it's not.
Penny 告诉我大家都怕我了
Penny told me that everyone's scared of me.
啊? 啥?
What? What?
你说那些干什么?
Why would she say that?
你知道她喝多了 对吧?
You know she drinks, right?
怎么会?
What?
没有 她说得对 我想告诉你
No, she's right, and I just want you to know
从现在开始 我要更在乎大家的感受
that from now on, I'm gonna be much more sensitive.
我不想让大家在我面前都如履薄冰
I don't want anyone walking on eggshells around me.
哦 呃 好吧 那么
Oh, well, okay, then, uh,
有件事我一直想要告诉你
one thing I've been meaning to tell you
公司不再为我们提供咖啡了
is that the company is gonna stop paying for our coffee.
没问题 什么时候开始啊?
No problem. When does that start?
五个月前
Five months ago.
- 什么?!  - 是的
- What?!  - Yeah.
那是谁一直再为我咖啡买单?
Who's been paying for my coffee?
我们所有人
All of us.
是啊 钱是从脏话罐里面拿的
Yeah. It comes from the swear jar
每一次你骂人我们就往脏话罐里投钱
we put money in when you curse.
还有什么是我不知道的?
What else don't I know about?
呃 你知道你有个私人洗手间是吧?
Uh, well, you know your private bathroom?
- 怎么了?  - 那是给整层楼的人用的
- Yeah?  - That was supposed to be for the whole floor.
- 你开玩笑的吧  - 不 不
- You're kidding.  - No, no.
没关系的 这只是对轮椅姐Kathy来说不方便而已
It's okay. It only really affected Wheelchair Kathy,
她又回到医院去了
and she's back in the hospital now,
所以事情都解决了
so it all worked out.
- 我感觉很内疚啊  - 是啊
- I feel so bad.  - Yeah.
你也许不应该
Well, then, maybe you shouldn't have
给她取"轮椅姐Kathy"这个绰号
named her "Wheelchair Kathy."
哦 天啊!
Oh, my God!
我以为每个人都很喜欢我 但我却是一个怪兽
I thought everybody liked me, but I'm just a monster.
但你是可爱的那种 怪兽公司里面独眼的那个家伙一样
But a cute one, like that, uh, eyeball guy in Monsters, Inc.
不 我糟透了
No, I'm the worst.
我是个糟糕的人
I'm a terrible person.
好了 别哭 没关系的
Come on, don't cry. It's okay.
有关系
It's not okay.
- 我怎么还能在这继续工作呢  - 哦
- How can I even work here anymore?  - Oh.
- 因为这个公司需要你啊  - 没事的
- Because this company needs you.  - It's fine.
我们不介意为你的咖啡买单
We don't mind paying for the coffee.
我不能让你们这样做
I can't let you do that.
也许我们能
Maybe we could get you
弄台意大利特浓咖啡机放在你办公室
an espresso machine for your office.
那真是极好的
I guess that would be all right.
好吧
All right.
看到没?
See? You don't have
你不需要说刻薄的话来得到你想要的东西
to be mean to get what you want.
你说得对
You're right.
那关于我私人洗手间的事怎么说呢?
Now where did we land on my bathroom?
嘿
Hey.
你好
Hello.
怎么这么晚还不睡?
How come you're up so late?
几个小时前
I posted the last episode
我上传了旗乐无穷最终集
of Fun with Flags hours ago,
现在一个评论都没收到
and not a single person cared enough to comment.
所有的功夫都白费了
All that effort for nothing.
嗯 我懂你的感受
Mm. I know how you feel.
我今天去把一个人所有的研究工作都扔掉了
I spent the day throwing out a man's entire career,
只剩下了一瓶上了年头的香槟
and all that's left is an old bottle of champagne
还有Raj以为我们没看到他偷偷拿了的
and a naked lady pen that Raj took
那只裸体女人模样的笔
when he thought no one was looking.
这不是一回事
It's not the same thing.
我觉得你一点都不懂我的感受
I don't think you know how I feel at all.
你觉得很难过?
Sad?
嗯 你还真懂我
Hmm. You do get me.
有人评论了
Someone left a comment.
是吗 他们怎么说?
Yeah. What did they say?
"很遗憾你的节目完结了
"Too bad your show is done.
我还挺喜欢的"
I kind of liked it."
Leonard 你听到了没?
Leonard, did you hear that?
哦 人们的心都要碎了呀!
Oh, the people are heartbroken!
我不能让这节目在这世界上消失!
I can't take this away from the world!
旗乐无穷回归了!
Fun with Flags is back!
恭喜啊
Congratulations.
让我们庆祝吧!
Let's celebrate!
Sheldon啊
Sheldon,
这不是留给你的啊!
that wasn't for you!
哦 不 我不打算喝它
Oh, no, I'm not going to drink it.
我只是想听盖子打开的时候嘭的一声
I just wanted to hear the pop.
我知道会它会响 但心里还是怕怕的呢
Yeah, I knew it was coming. Still scary.
喂 LeVar Burton?
LeVar Burton?
喂 LeVar Burton!
LeVar Burton!
啊 你在这干嘛?
Ugh. What are you doing here?
你说我不能打电话
You told me not to call,
我觉得没有别的办法把这个好消息告诉你了
and I didn't know how else to give you the good news.
旗乐无穷回归了 你可以出现在下一集里了
Fun with Flags is back, and you can be in the next episode.
Wil Wheaton告诉我得装个大铁门
Wil Wheaton said, get a gate.
- 我不知道为什么我偏没有装大铁门  - 你...
- I don't know why I didn't get a gate.  - You...
至少先听听我的提议
At least listen to the premise.
既然你是在德国出生的
Since you were born in Germany,
我觉得我们能谈论一下德国的旗子
I thought we could talk about German flags.
不如你打扮成像个纳粹的样子好不好?
How do you feel about dressing up like a swastika?